Aegis Crypter 2017 the new upgrade


The new upgrade features:
 
Add Digital signature

Auto sync cloud vbs stub keep vbs is fud 

Fixes some bugs
-----------------------------------
You can make your own stub contain stub source code ,temporarily is free
If you know very simple programming,
You can easily make your own fud stub, even sales your stub.

General stub will support most of exe progarm , contain native exe, .net 2.0, net 4.0, 

support windows system 2000,xp,2003,vista,win7,win8,win10

Bypass Avast deep screen, Eset nod32 memory scan , Microsoft Defender memory scan,etc.

Automatic check upgrade crypter builder and stub

Free stub also will continue to update


Http://www.aegiscrypter.com/

Email: aegiscrypter@gmail.com

Video: http://youtu.be/cuwdl68uwJk


Recommended scanning service

http://nodistribute.com/

http://www.refud.me/

Prohibited uploaded to scanning service

http://www.virustotal.com/

http://www.virscan.org/

http://virusscan.jotti.org/



PS: bypass gmail

Gmail now check zip, rar, 7z ,etc files, if the file contains the EXE file, Gmail will not allow you to send attachments

The solution
1,First set show file extensions in your windows
2.By WinRAR package your files to .rar
3.Change your file extension to .uue (example name.rar-->name.uue)
4.since .uue file also can open by winrar open
exe-->rar-->.uue

